export const QuizData = [
    // Q1
    {
        question: "What is the range of values that can be stored by int datatype in C?",
        options: ["-(2^31) to (2^31) - 1", "-256 to 255", "-(2^63) to (2^63) - 1", "0 to (2^31) - 1"],
        answer: 1
    },
    // Q2
    {
        question: "How is an array initialized in C language?",
        options: ["int a = {1, 2, 3};", "int a[] = new int[3]", "int a[3] = {1, 2, 3};", "int a(3) = [1, 2, 3];"],
        answer: 3
    },
    // Q3
    {
        question: "How is the 3rd element in an array accessed based on pointer notation?",
        options: ["*a + 3", "*(*a + 3)", "&(a + 3)", "*(a + 3)"],
        answer: 4
    },
    // Q4
    {
        question: "How are String represented in memory in C?",
        options: ["The object of some class.", "An array of characters.", "Same as other primitive data types.", "LinkedList of characters."],
        answer: 2
    },
    // Q5
    {
        question: "What is the disadvantage of arrays in C?",
        options: ["Elements of an array can be accessed in constant time.", "The amount of memory to be allocated should be known beforehand.", "Elements are stored in contiguous memory blocks.", "Multiple other data structures can be implemented using arrays."],
        answer: 2
    },
    // Q6
    {
        question: "Which of the following is the proper syntax for declaring macros in C?",
        options: ["#define long long ll", "#define ll", "#define long long", "#define ll long long"],
        answer: 4
    },
    // Q7
    {
        question: "Which of the following is an exit controlled loop?",
        options: ["do-while loop.", "While loop.", "For loop.", "None of the above."],
        answer: 1
    },
    // Q8
    {
        question: "What is the size of the int data type (in bytes) in C?",
        options: ["8", "2", "4", "1"],
        answer: 3
    },
    // Q9
    {
        question: "How to declare a double-pointer in C?",
        options: ["int *val", "int **val", "int &val", "int *&val"],
        answer: 2
    },
    // Q10
    {
        question: "If p is an integer pointer with a value 1000, then what will the value of p + 5 be?",
        options: ["1005", "1004", "1010", "1020"],
        answer: 4
    },
];